Daisuke Nagata

Full Stack | Blockchain Engineer

☑ daisukenagata0209@gmail.com



ABOUT ME

Energetic and Passionate web programmer aimed to use knowledge for web site and web application development. My focus is on clean, elegant, and efficient codes. I have solid experience in React.js, Next.js, TypeScript and Node.js. I have been educated and trained in modern IT techniques. I worked with a myriad of web and mobile technologies, frameworks, practiced both building apps from scratch and contributing to large pre-existing projects with legacy code. Over the last 4 years, mainly focusing on blockchain technology such as Solidity | Web3 | Ether | Polka | Solana | Solana-Web3. Really, eager to participate any DEFI & DApp firms and boost the project with my enthusiasm & experience.

Throughout my career, I have completed many web app projects across different verticals, ranging from large companies to startups. I always keep up with the latest news and developments in the web and blockchain world through meetups and self-teaching. Always be hungry for learning new technology & improving myself, especially on blockchain scope. Currently, my main focus is on the Cosmos SDK and Aptos move.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Remote Work

April 2022 — Current

I've developed number of Shopify Websites using JavaScript, Node.js and MySQL database. I'm very familiar with JavaScript libraries such as React.js, Vue.js and Angular.js I have rich experience in Shopify and MySQL database.

In particular, I have a wealth of experience with smart contracts (solidity and rust). Working as freelancer, has redesigned and rebuilt 5+ websites, 3 large websites from scratch, 5+ decentralized applications, 3 NFT Marketplaces and developed 20+ ERC20, ERC721, ERC1155 smart contracts, DAO, Defi, etc. He also participated in smart contract audits and gas optimization. So smart contracts are my best technologies other than web technology Technologies used:

React Next.js Node.js Express.js Web3.js Smart contract Dex Defi UI / UX Design

Software Engineer

at Crowderia, Sri Lanka

as Freelancer

November 2020 — April 2022

Contributions:

- ERP for Inventory management, Profit handling etc. using Amazon API.
- Mobile Application for the scenario of, using Web Application APIs finding nearest retailer deals in a locale and showing the locations of shops in the map.

Technologies used:

CakePHP MySQL AWS AngularJS PhoneGap(Android) Google Map

Web Developer

at Setronica, United States

March 2018 — May 2020

- What I had done:Dropdown Menu of Navbar animation Effect using CSS3.
- Did advanced JavaScript functional programming.
- Designed a MongoDB database.
- Developed software using RESTful APIs with Express.js.
- Handled JavaScript UX framework prototyping.

Technologies used:

HTML5 CSS3 Javascript NoSQL React RestAPI Node

IT Executive

at Birds Of Paradise, Scotland

July 2014 — August 2017

Worked as pert time employee in my educational period. In this period done several tasks like -

- Excel & Google Sheet automation by writing script
- Testing web based software
- Developing a static website
- Writing Technical Documents

Technologies used:

eact Redux TailwindCSS Typescript Next Web3 DeF

SKILLS & TOOLS

Frontend

React / Next

HTML / CSS / Javascipt

Vue / Nuxt

Material UI

Tailwind CSS

TypeScript / Styled-Component

Backend

PHP / Codelgniter / Laravel

Node / Nest

Express MongoDB

Blockchain

Web3.js / ethers.js

Solidity

Smart Contract

Defi Dex

Golang

Rust

Cosmos

EDUCATION

Software Engineering, Tokyo University, Tokyo, Japan Bachelor of Science (Information Technology) 2014 — 2017

AWARDS

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science

LANGUAGE

Japanese (Native)

English (Fluent)